export default data = [
  {
      question: "Posters of the local rock band were displayed in store windows to promote the sale of their _____ tickets.",
      options: ["journey","traffic","concert","record"],
      correct_option: "concert"
  },
  {
      question: "Maria didn’t want to deliver the bad news to David about his failing the job interview. She herself was quite _____ about it. ",
      options: ["awful","drowsy","tragic","upset"],
      correct_option: "upset"
  },
  {
      question: "The newcomer speaks with a strong Irish _____; he must be from Ireland.",
      options: ["accent","identity","gratitude","signature"],
      correct_option: "accent"
  },
  {
      question: "Although Maggie has been physically _____ to her wheelchair since the car accident, she does not limit herself to indoor activities. ",
      options: ["ceased","committed","confined","conveyed"],
      correct_option: "confined"
  },
  {
      question: "All passengers riding in cars are required to fasten their seatbelts in order to reduce the risk of _____ in case of an accident. ",
      options: ["injury","offense","sacrifice","victim"],
      correct_option: "injury"
  },
  {
      question: "The principal of this school is a man of exceptional _____. He sets aside a part of his salary for a scholarship fund for children from needy families.",
      options: ["security","maturity","facility","generosity"],
      correct_option: "generosity"
  },
  {
      question: "The science teacher always _____ the use of the laboratory equipment before she lets her students use it on their own.",
      options: ["tolerates","associates","demonstrates","exaggerates"],
      correct_option: "demonstrates"
  },
  {
      question: "Most of the area is covered by woods, where bird species are so _____ that it is a paradise for birdwatchers.",
      options: ["durable","private","realistic","numerous"],
      correct_option: "numerous"
  },
  {
      question: "In most cases, the committee members can reach agreement quickly. _____, however, they differ greatly in opinion and have a hard time making decisions.",
      options: ["Occasionally","utomatically","Enormously","Innocently"],
      correct_option: "Occasionally"
  },
  {
      question: "Many people try to save a lot of money before _____, since having enough money would give them a sense of security for their future.",
      options: ["isolation","promotion","retirement","announcement"],
      correct_option: "retirement"
  },
  {
      question: "In winter, our skin tends to become dry and _____, a problem which is usually treated by applying lotions or creams.",
      options: ["alert","itchy","steady","flexible"],
      correct_option: "itchy"
  },
  {
      question: "Benson married Julie soon after he had _____ her heart and gained her parents’ approval.",
      options: ["conquered","estimated","guaranteed","intensified"],
      correct_option: "conquered"
  },
  {
      question: "The recent flood completely _____ my parents’ farm. The farmhouse and fruit trees were all gone and nothing was left.",
      options: ["ruined","cracked","hastened","neglected"],
      correct_option: "ruined"
  },
  {
      question: "The results of this survey are not reliable because the people it questioned were not a typical or _____ sample of the entire population that was studied. ",
      options: ["primitive","spiritual","representative","informative"],
      correct_option: "representative"
  },
  {
      question: "In line with the worldwide green movement, carmakers have been working hard to make their new models more _____ friendly to reduce pollution.",
      options: ["liberally","individually","financially","environmentally"],
      correct_option: "environmentally"
  },
]
